Guide to the Dimock Gallery records, 1963-2011 RG0087
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibition files, 1966-2011; Series 7; 36 Linear Feet 24 record center cartoons
  - Exhibition files, 1992-1993 (Box 13)
    This box contains the following materials: • Annual Awards Show 4/8-29/93 • Literacy Volunteers of America Benefit April 21, 1993 • GW Fine Arts Faculty Show 2/25 – 3/25/1993 • A. Clarke Bedford Lunch Bag Talk 3/3/93 • Panel Discussion on Mural Painting • Jan. 28 – Feb 13, 1993 Fire and Water, Ozdogan and Smith • Patriots and Prophets: Outsider Art from the Washington Area Collections. 10/12/92 – 11/3/92 • Annual Student Show 11/12 - 12/3/1992 • Visual Communications Alumni Show 12/10/92 – 1/21/93 • Paintings by Robert W. Kenny 6/12 – 6/30/1992 • MFA Spring Thesis Candidate Show 5/7- 29/1992 • Annual Awards Show 4/2 - 4/30/1992 • Fine Arts Faculty Exhibition 2/13 - 3/19/92 • MFA Winter Thesis Candidate Show 1/9 – 2/6/92
  - Exhibition files, 1993 (Box 14)
    This box contains the following materials: • MFA Spring Thesis Candidate show (incl. Kaskie, Liberace, Stanier, Montalbano) • Return of Photographic material • Brother Thomas Exhibition 10/7/93 – 10/28/93 (Coll. artist) • Annual Student Show 11/4 – 12/2/1993
  - Exhibition files, 1994 (Box 15)
    This box contains the following materials: • Annual Student Show, 11/3 – 11/30/1994 • Howard Hodgkin Prints: Vision and Collaboration, 9/22 – 10/26/94 • Annual Awards Show, April 7 – 28, 1994 • MFA Spring Thesis Candidate Show, Grp I May 5-18, 1994, Grp II May 25-June 9, 1994 • Literacy Volunteers of America, April 21, 1994 • Annual Awards Show, 1994 • William Woodward and Frank Wright, 2/24 - 3/24/1994 (Two person faculty shows) • Book signing possibilities • John K. Hillers and William Henry Jackson, 19th Century Photographs of the American West from the GW Permanent Collection, 12/9/1993 – 1/29/1994
  - Exhibition files, 1995 (Box 16)
    This box contains the following materials: • Description of Chagall prints, written by Erin Loftus, panel • Prizes from Annual Award Show, 4/6 – 4/26/1995 • MFA Spring Thesis Candidate Show, 5/4 – 5/18/1995, 5/25 – 6/9/1995 • Colonial Inauguration Parent Reception, 8/23/95 • Images of George Washington • GW (Still) BMOC: Images of GW, Past and Present, 1995 • Legacy Reception 10/14/95 • Oleg Kudryashov: Moscow Remembered, Hand-colored drypoint compositions, reliefs and constructions, 9/21-10/25/95 • Annual Student Show, 11/2-29/95
  - Exhibition files, 1995-1996 (Box 17)
    This box contains the following materials: • entire box contains files regarding that exhibition • 175th anniversary of the university • Research from Corcoran archives, Penny Dwyer notes, Henry Bacon's pets, press photos, reviews • painting lent to Hirshel and Addler in NY for alumni event
  - Exhibition files, 1996 (Box 18)
    This box contains the following materials: • Benson Bond Moore • Public Programs (Moore) • Benson Bond Moore's Works on Paper Regional Landscapes, Portraits, and Wildlife, 1920 – 1940, December 8, 1994 – Jan. 18, 1995 • Recent Acquisitions to the GW Dimock Gallery 2/2 – 2/14/95 • Full Time Faculty Exh. Feb 23 – March 22, 1995 • David Lloyd Kreeger lecture • 1996 Prizes • Annual Awards Show April 11 – May 1, 1996 • Mariana Pineda Sept. 12 – Oct. 25, 1996 • Mrs. Weingold's Tea Oct. 8 • Reunion Weekend • Annual Student Show Nov. 7 – Dec. 4, 1996
  - Exhibition files, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
    This box contains the following materials: • Site-Specific Sculpture Program (1997) • Valentine's Day Tea (February 13, 1998) • President's Dinner-Hippo (1996)
  - Exhibition files, 1997-1998 (Box 20)
    This box contains the following materials: • 2 Boxes of Slides, each labeled: "Kelly Ford, Condition Report Slides of Exhibition the Digital Atelier" • MFA Spring Thesis Candidate Show, 4/30 – 5/22/98 • Annual Awards Show, 4/2 – 4/22/98 • Foon Sham Lecture w/WPAC, April 22, 1998 • Faculty Emeritus Exhibition, 2/12 - 3/19/98 • Valentine Tea, 1998 • Annual Student Show • Narkiss Lecture, Nov. 18 or 19, Cancelled • Exhibiting the Digital Atelier: Prints by Unique Editions and Participating Artists, 12/11/97 – 1/30/98 • Exhibiting the Digital Atelier: Programs, January 14th and 15th • Mixed Mediums: Cycles of the Spiritual, Sept. 11 – Oct. 30, 1997 • Lydia Bodnar-Balahutrak ["Mixed Mediums" artist] • Sharon Kopriva ["Mixed Mediums" artist] • Programs: SA 10/17
  - Exhibition files, 1998-1999 (Box 21)
    This box contains the following materials: • MFA #2 • Partners' Committee T (1998) • GW Ceramics • 10th anniversary • 25th anniversary
  - Exhibition files, 1999-2000 (Box 22)
    This box contains the following materials: • Japonisme -Washington Print Club • Boggs-Regarding George Washington • Art of Exile-Tibetan Children's Art • Worlds of Transformation
  - Exhibition Files, 2001-2011 (Box 23)
    This box contains the following materials: Millennium Seminar, Sandra Myers (1999-2001), Goya: "Los Caprichos" (2001).
  - Marvin Center 3rd Floor Gallery, 1980-1988 (Box 24)